The time has come.
Let us check our personal effects.
All clear, sir.
And now, our appearances.
And a final check of our verbal etiquette.
All set, please. Will do my best, please.
I feel nothing but anxiety about this,
but we've done everything we could.
Now, onward...
THE PRESTIGIOUS SCHOOL'S INTERVIEW
To Eden College's interview!
It's so big!
Well, it is one of this country's top schools.
And there are so many examinees...
They're all our rivals.
Anya, are you going to
be okay in this crowd?
I'll be okay, please.
Let us go, then.
This feeling...
There's no doubt about it.
I've experienced this many times.
Someone is watching us. Could it be...
Is there an enemy hidden in this crowd?
An enemy?
I feel someone's gaze...
No, that's not it.
I'm not the only one being watched.
It's always an unpleasant
feeling to be observed like this.
There.
Four in the overhead passage.
Four in the bell tower.
More in the buildings to the left and right.
I have information on most
of the staff at this school.
Those... are the instructors.
They're observing every action that
everyone is taking and scoring them
to see if they're worthy of this school.
Which means... the exam has already begun.
I need you two to be on your guard.
We're being watched by the examiners.
Huh?
We'll do this just as we practiced.
D-68, fail.
A-12, fail.
G-114, pass.
I must say, the examinees
this year lack refinement.
They all lack true elegance.
Good morning, Housemaster.
Eden College
<Housemaster>
It displeases me to know their crude feet
are trudging upon the blessed
ground of our school.
Elegance creates tradition.
Elegance is what truly makes
this world a paradise.
Fail any family lacking
elegance immediately.
Yes, sir.
Hm?
Oho...
It appears that not all hope has been lost.
They are paying their respects
to the statue of our founder?!
I, Twilight, am a man of a thousand faces.
Becoming exactly the person my target
wants me to be is mere child's play.
Behold!
I haven't the slightest clue
as to who this gentleman is,
but everything should be fine as
long as I do what Loid is doing.
Baldy head!
S-So elegant!
How very elegant!
Who is that family?
K-212. They are the Forgers, sir.
Their daughter Anya just barely passed
the written exam with a score of 31.
Absolutely not elegant!
And such awful penmanship!
So the father has remarried?
Might they be an impromptu
family for admission purposes?
I am not certain. We must investigate.
We must ascertain whether
or not they have true elegance.
We'll confirm your admission numbers here.
G-114. Please go to Hall 1.
Ah, A-12. Please enter Hall 2.
I see they're wasting no
time with the screening.
K-212. Please head to Hall 1.
We're still being observed.
Don't let your guard down.
It's so nerve-racking
being watched like this...
I need to pick my nose.
Absolutely not.
Oh, no!
I've accidentally fallen into
the gutter, and I can't get out!
Uh... That's too blatant if
they're trying to test us.
Oh, no. Whatever shall I do?
Perhaps they're thinking
he might be a threat,
Ah, I don't know what I should do.
but no one is trying to go near him.
Who knew there'd be a gutter here?
But if he is part of the test,
we must deal with this accordingly.
I'm so shocked. I'm really stuck.
Papa! Mama! There is someone
who needs our help, please!
Let us save him!
Are you all right, lad?
Oh, no! I've slipped and I cannot get up!
This is all for merits... More merits!
Precisely.
You're heading to an interview. You wouldn't
dare sully your clothes with sewage.
Now, how will you elegantly get through—
Are you hurt?
Use my hanky, please.
Make sure you go to
the infirmary, just in case.
Clearly, I expected too much.
In the end, they were just some
commoners from the countryside.
Do not think for a second that you can
set foot in our house of
learning wearing soiled clothes.
Throw K-212 out immediately.
Oh, no... These people are
going to fail because of me.
Um, I'm so sorr—
Thank goodness we anticipated this,
and prepared a change of
clothes just in case!
Who in the world would
ever anticipate that?!
Besides, your grey suit seems to
fit the attire at this school more.
If I had continued wearing my previous suit,
we would've been mistaken for
commoners from the countryside.
Thank you for giving us the
opportunity to change, lad.
On top of everything else,
they even thanked the boy!
Brilliant... So smart, and elegant!
Curse you and your cunning, Loid Forger.
Housemaster, we are supposed
to be testing the child.
Silence!
Children learn from their parents' example!
Yes. The parents of a child who scores 30
points must also be only worth 30 points!
I'll make you reveal your true identity yet!
Oh, no!
The animals have escaped the farmhouse!
You're really going this far, Eden College?!
Hey, don't push me!
Just go, you moron!
Mommy! Mommy, Mommy!
Shut up!
Are they trying to see if we reveal
our true selves in an emergency?
We'll be playing right into the
examiners' hands if we panic.
Do not break Formation D.
We will show these animals
nothing but benevolence!
Hey.
Who told you to go that far?
Wait...
It wasn't you, Housemaster?
Impossible! Is this...
an actual accident?!
There are some very important
people among the examinees!
Go stop this mess before they're hurt!
I'm the Vice Minister of
the Ministry of Finance!
Hell if I care! I'm the
CEO of the Central Bank!
Wait! Father!
Well done, you!
Are you all right?
Loid!
It's happening to Miss Anya again.
The mass panic must've hit her.
The test is the last thing
I need to worry about now.
That must be the leader of this herd.
That's the one I need to stop,
but I'll have to use my gun—
No...
Please look after Miss Anya for a moment.
Yor?
I-It's not what you think!
I once learned about pressure points that
can stop one's movements in a yoga class!
I-I figured they might work on cows, too!
Please don't look at me like that!
Ms. Cow?
Is she scared?
That's dangerous, Anya!
S'okay, please. Don't be scared.
What are you—
They're gonna go home now.
Apparently so.
Thankfully, no one was hurt.
E-Ele...
Ele-le... Ele-le-le-le...
Elegance!
Housemaster?
Forger!
He's...
one of the housemasters.
Is he in charge of this exam?
Y-You helped us avoid a crisis. I thank you.
And... you have bested me for today.
To give us all time to collect
ourselves after this chaos,
we will be delaying the
start of the interviews.
Return to your hall once you've
had a moment to tidy yourselves.
Your family has the right
to apply to our school.
Sir...
It looks like we've avoided failure.
I humbly thank you for your generosity.
But have no fear.
We anticipated something like this...
and prepared another change of clothes.
This isn't about elegance anymore!
These people are just scary!
The Forgers successfully make
it to the actual interview.
You truly thought you could apply to
our school without even knowing that?
Huh?
Well? Cat got your tongue?
Um, uh...
Thank you very much.
What kind of answer was that?!
I've been a spy for over a decade,
and for the first time...
I'm actually nervous.
Even when I infiltrated the ranks
of an evil terrorist group,
or when I managed to stop the launch of
a missile with one second remaining...
I never found it so hard to
breathe as I do right now.
The fear of letting someone else
decide my success or failure...
Next, the Forgers.
Yep!
Yes, sir.
Yes, this is definitely going to be...
the most crucial moment of Operation Strix!
Please, have a seat.
Thank you for having us.
So you've come, Forgers.
The Forgers shall prevail in this
game of information warfare.
First, we will begin by asking
the parents a few questions.
Walter Evans (59)
Housemaster of Dorm 5 <Malcom Hall>
Subject Taught: English
Personality: Mild-mannered • Sincere • Conservative
The housemaster of Dorm 5, Malcom Hall.
Mild-mannered, sincere, and conservative.
The students are very fond of him.
As long as we respond with
sincere, logical answers,
we'll score highly with him.
I was informed that this is your second
wife. May I ask how you two met?
I see we're getting straight to the point.
Eden College does prioritize
family values, after all.
I met my wife at the tailor shop that
handles this school's uniforms,
and I was in awe of her grace.
Ever since I lost my first wife,
I was hesitant to pursue another
relationship because of my daughter.
But the more we spoke, the more
I felt that she was a kindred spirit.
She is truly kind and cares
dearly about family.
I came to the conclusion that she'd
get along well with my daughter.
Ah... And what about you, Madam?
Well...
L-Loid is a wonderful person who
truly cares for his daughter.
He's also very considerate of me.
Ah, I'm happy to hear that you
have such a loving family.
Why would a beautiful girl like you choose
to be with a man who's got baggage?
That was rather uncouth, Master Swan.
Murdoch Swan (47)
Housemaster of Dorm 2 <Cline Hall>
Subject Taught: Economics
Personality: Arrogant • Greedy • Callous
The housemaster of Dorm 2, Cline Hall.
He's the only son of the former
headmaster, and a legacy hire.
Arrogant, greedy, and callous.
His wife filed for divorce last month,
and he just lost custody
of his daughter, as well.
Reviewing all of his previous
interview questions and comments,
he is clearly jealous of other families,
and takes out his frustrations on them.
It's best that we avoid provoking him.
Now for our next question.
Could you tell us why you
chose to apply to our school?
For only one reason, sir.
To get close to my target, Desmond!
The quality of the instructors at
this establishment is superior.
Of course, you are all very
knowledgeable and cultured,
but when it comes to teaching anything,
from patriotism to how to be an elite,
the instructors of the
prestigious Eden College
are second to none.
Henry Henderson (66)
Housemaster of Dorm 3 <Cecil Hall>
Subject Taught: History
Personality: Elegant
Elegantly done, Loid Forger.
I knew I saw potential in you.
Now then, how would the two
of you describe your daughter?
Please let us know about her
strengths and weaknesses.
Anya is an extremely curious child.
Her habit of sticking her nose where it
doesn't belong could be seen as a weakness,
but she is a truly intelligent child.
Intelligent?! Her?!
Shock!
Sometimes, it's like she
sees right through me,
Yikes...
which keeps me on my feet.
I would say her main shortcoming
is that she's a picky eater.
Ah...  And how would you describe
your parenting style, Madam?
Just like we practiced...
As you already know, I am
not her biological mother.
At first, I spoiled her quite often
in hopes that she would like me.
But for the sake of her future, I'm hoping
I can become a bit stricter at times.
We've been told that your
daughter is a picky eater.
What kind of meals do you cook at home?
Huh? C-Cook?
Um...
I actually do most of the cooking.
Though when I'm busy, my wife
is kind enough to cook for me.
Not that that's happened even once yet.
You're joking! What kind of wife
can't cook for her husband?!
You should probably be stricter with
yourself before you worry about that child.
Everyone has strengths and weaknesses.
She is extremely tidy and excels
at keeping our house spotless.
She is also an excellent
mother to my daughter.
Yes, well, both of those are
things women are expected to do.
That's—
I-It's all right, Loid.
Now, now...
Yes. Calm down.
Why are you getting irritated, Twilight?
She's not even your real wife.
A lovey-dovey hot couple? You make me sick.
I'll keep jabbing at you until you slip up.
If I can't make sure these two fail,
there's clearly no justice in this world.
He doesn't like Papa and Mama!
I need to do my best!
N-Next, let's ask the
young lady some questions.
Here it comes.
First, could you tell us
your name and address?
My name is Anya Holger!
My address is in... Berlint, West District...
128 Park... Avenue!
And what do you do on your
days off, young lady?
We go to moozeums...
and eat operas...
Good. These were questions we anticipated.
What would you like to do once
you get into this school?
Um, uh...
What was I supposed to say?
In my case, I first need to
participate in a social gathering,
and get to the bottom of what the boss of
the enemy organization, Desmond, is planning.
I-I want to find out what the boss
of the organization is planning!
What in the world are you saying?! Hello?!
The boss of the organization?
Maybe you meant the headmaster.
I do apologize. My daughter
is rather ambitious.
She's extremely curious about the headmaster,
since he's clearly made it to the top.
Oho...
The desire to learn from her
predecessors at such an early age...
That's quite elegant.
Do you happen to know the name
of the principal, young lady?
Um, B-Be...
Yes. Benedict Ivan Goodfellow.
Mr. Benedick Advent Goodheller.
Hmm... Then,
could you tell us how hard you would have
to work in order to succeed like him?
Yes. Like getting through
the jungle with no supplies,
and dancing with death over
and over to get brave!
That was the training montage the
protagonist of her spy cartoon did yesterday.
S-Such incredible resolve!
It appears as though I have
underestimated this young lady.
I don't think you have to do quite that much.
Let's change the subject.
What does your father do for a living?
He's a sp—a speshulist in
mental health. A very good one.
Hm? Are you a little stuffed up?
Then how do you feel about your new mother?
She is very nice.
But she's scary sometimes.
If you were to give your parents
a score, what might that be?
A perfect 100 points.
My Papa and Mama are both so
much fun, and I love them very much.
I want to be with them forever.
Tch. God, no one needs this rubbish.
In that case, would you score your
old mother or your new mother higher?
Come now, Master Swan...
Is there a problem?
May I respectfully request
a different question?
Absolutely not. If you do not
answer, you will lose points.
I don't know exactly how she
ended up in that orphanage,
but her actual parents
are probably already...
Ma...ma...
Anya...
Mama...
I see, I see.
So you do prefer your old mother.
This is too cruel!
Please calm down, Yor.
But this is just—
We need to remain calm for
the sake of this mission.
We have plenty of students here who live
away from their parents in our dorms.
If she's going to cry over
every little trifling thing,
she'll never survive at our establishment!
So what if he's being slanderous?
We are nothing more than a pretend family.
Trifling? You call this trifling?
This is nothing.
Now, now, Mrs. Second Wife.
Don't snap at me just because
she loves her real mother more.
Oh, I feel so much better.
Restrain yourself...
Twilight!
I do beg your pardon.
There was a mosquito.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Hey, where are you going?!
The interview's not over yet!
If making light of a child's feelings is part
of your establishment's educational policies,
then I'm afraid we have
chosen the wrong school.
You fiend! You dare
disgrace our fine school?!
Come now, you two.
Please excuse us.
Don't think you'll ever walk
through our gates again!
That's quite enough, Master Swan.
Are you taking issue with my methods?
He may be the former headmaster,
Now, now...
but my father's influence
within this school is still strong.
It'd be wise for you to
watch that mouth of yours.
Hey! Hurry up and call the next one in!
...the instructors of the
prestigious Eden College
are second to none.
If all I can do is curry
favor with the authorities,
I have no right to call myself an educator.
I must ask, who truly disgraced our school?
Huh?!
Wha—
Hmm...
That was rather elegant,
if I do say so myself.
Now, will you be able to face
the instructors at Eden head-on,
Forgers?
Yeah... We definitely failed.
I-I'll go make us some tea.
I've failed yet again as a spy.
I let unnecessary feelings get
in the way of the mission.
Papa...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't do better
on my tests.
It's all right, Anya. You have
no reason to apologize.
You don't want to go to
a school like that, do you?
But I want to go to school...
Huh?
If this mission fails...
I have to go to school or...
...we won't be together anymore.
Anya...
If she fails, of course,
our life here together will be...
But that doesn't matter.
I'm just worried how this may affect my work.
Hmm... But to be honest,
Hell will freeze over before you pass.
Shock!
I-I'm sure everything will be okay!
It'll all work out!
The grandpa with the glasses and
the grandpa with the half-glasses
were really nice!
Yes, exactly!
I'm sure they'll vouch for us!
Let's believe in them.
Spies don't believe in anyone
other than themselves.
They always expect the worst-case
scenarios and prepare for them.
I want to be with them forever.
But... Maybe just a little bit...
Yes. Let's leave the result to fate,
and try to recover from how
exhausting that exam was.
Right now, just for a little bit...
To our family's bright future!
Something just fell!
Our family portrait fell to the floor.
It just fell...
What will become
of their mission?
WILL THEY PASS OR FAIL